http://www.burkecandy.com/pages/privacy-policy

Brittle
Flying T's (Turtles)
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this website only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
COLLECTION OF INFORMATIONWe collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfil you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.
COOKIE/TRACKING TECHNOLOGYThe Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information.
DISTRIBUTION OF INFORMATIONWe may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITYYour personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
PRIVACY CONTACT INFORMATIONIf you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:By e-mail: orders@burkecandy.comBy Phone: 414-964-7327
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
Join our mailing list
You’ve successfully subscribed!
RETURN TO SITE
© BURKE CANDY & INGREDIENTS. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
Shop Chocolates
Shop Ingredients
Capabilities
About Us
Chocolate Pairings
Community Events
Trade Shows
Associations & Certifications
Collections
Caramels
Chocolates
Bark
Brittle
Flying T's (Turtles)
Mint Meltaways
Toffees
Ice Cream Inclusions
Signature Collection
Special instructions for seller
Subtotal
Shipping & taxes calculated at checkout
It appears that your cart is currently empty!
Continue Browsing
Net Orders Checkout
Item
Price
Qty
Total
Subtotal
$0.00
Mozambique
Myanmar (Burma)
Namibia
Nauru
Nepal
Netherlands
Netherlands Antilles
New Caledonia
New Zealand
Nicaragua
Zimbabwe
AlabamaAlaskaAmerican SamoaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFederated States of MicronesiaFloridaGeorgiaGuamHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarshall IslandsMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaNorthern Mariana IslandsOhioOklahomaOregonPalauPennsylvaniaPuerto RicoRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirgin IslandsVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces Pacific
Shipping Methods
